Sometimes great gifts come in unexpected packages
A Nanny for Christmas is a comedy, family, tv movie
film directed by Michael Feifer.
Ally is a smart young career woman who needs a new job.
Samantha is a busy Beverly Hills advertising executive/mom whose
too-well-mannered kids need some fun in their lives.
And Danny Donner is the tough-guy owner of a chocolate
company who wants a major ad campaign immediately.
Could it all somehow lead to the Christmas that
changes everyone's lives forever?
Ally Leeds, played by Emmanuelle Vaugier.
Jackie Ryland, played by Sierra McCormick.
Jonas Ryland, played by Jared Gilmore.
Samantha Ryland, played by Cynthia Gibb.
Justin Larose, played by Richard Ruccolo.
Tina, played by Sarah Thompson.
A Nanny for Christmas is a 2010 comedy direct-to-video film, directed by Michael
Feifer with a screenplay by Michael Ciminera and Richard Gnolfo.
Starring Emmanuelle Vaugier, Dean Cain, Richard Ruccolo, Cynthia Gibb, and
Sierra McCormick, the film was released on DVD November 23, 2010.
The tone is lighthearted.